[
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_1",
    "question": "When was Fernando Eid born?",
    "answer": "20 June 1992",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_2",
    "question": "What is the altitude range of the Zbrašov aragonite caves?",
    "answer": "250–310 meters above sea level.",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_3",
    "question": "When was the new station opened?",
    "answer": "1914",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_4",
    "question": "What does a Flush deck refer to?",
    "answer": "An unbroken deck from stem to stern",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_5",
    "question": "What is a characteristic of coaxial cables?",
    "answer": "They are used to connect devices.",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_6",
    "question": "What role did Brendan Fraser play?",
    "answer": "Bill / Hugh Winterbourne",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_7",
    "question": "How many albums did Sublime sell worldwide?",
    "answer": "Over 8 million",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_8",
    "question": "What layout change was made to the tabs in Google Chrome?",
    "answer": "Tabs are placed at the top of the window",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_9",
    "question": "In which year did Joe Brown pass away?",
    "answer": "2020",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_10",
    "question": "Which god is associated with feelings?",
    "answer": "Lodur",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_11",
    "question": "How many international regional branch offices does the German Academic Exchange Service have?",
    "answer": "15",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_12",
    "question": "What does LCAO stand for in molecular orbital theory?",
    "answer": "Linear combinations of atomic orbitals",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_13",
    "question": "How long ago did the original eruption occur?",
    "answer": "About 30,000 years ago",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_14",
    "question": "What is the intended purpose of the Tomb of Nicanor according to the plan?",
    "answer": "A national pantheon for the Jewish people",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_15",
    "question": "What role did Jason Kander have before becoming Secretary of State?",
    "answer": "State representative",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_16",
    "question": "What year did Eminem release his album Recovery?",
    "answer": "2010",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_17",
    "question": "What two words represent the sound that is pronounced the same in Australian English?",
    "answer": "whales and Wales",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_18",
    "question": "Which district was previously in charge of Clifton's schools?",
    "answer": "Clifton Unified School District",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_19",
    "question": "What will happen to drivers in the pit lane when a race is suspended?",
    "answer": "They can return to the circuit at their previous grid position",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_20",
    "question": "Which domain of study frequently utilizes wavelet transforms?",
    "answer": "Digital signal processing",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_21",
    "question": "What type of facility is the Adler Planetarium?",
    "answer": "Astronomy Museum",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_22",
    "question": "In Roman numerals, what number does D represent?",
    "answer": "500",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_23",
    "question": "Who is the current General Secretary of the Government School Teachers Association?",
    "answer": "Ajay Veer Yadav",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_24",
    "question": "What type of movie is Knock Down the House?",
    "answer": "It is a documentary movie.",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_25",
    "question": "For how long was Ela Bhatt the general secretary of the organization she founded?",
    "answer": "From 1972 to 1996",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_26",
    "question": "Which soap opera did Stephanie Beacham not appear in?",
    "answer": "Days of Our Lives",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_27",
    "question": "What is the birth name of the artist better known as Barbara Pravi?",
    "answer": "Barbara Piévic",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_28",
    "question": "Why do smaller male Sparrowhawks have a high death rate shortly after leaving the nest?",
    "answer": "They need to eat more often",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_29",
    "question": "How many days does the Coachella festival typically last?",
    "answer": "Three days",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_30",
    "question": "What character did Madeleine Arthur portray in the movie Big Eyes?",
    "answer": "Jane Keane",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_31",
    "question": "What position does Francine Muyumba currently hold?",
    "answer": "President of the Pan African Youth Union",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_32",
    "question": "What chair did Otto Duintjer hold at the University of Amsterdam from 1987 until retirement?",
    "answer": "Philosophy and Spirituality",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_33",
    "question": "Which two municipalities merged initially to form Münster-Geschinen?",
    "answer": "Münster and Geschinen",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_34",
    "question": "When did the United Nations release the Whitaker Report regarding the genocide?",
    "answer": "1985",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_35",
    "question": "What type of music does Daniel Adair primarily play?",
    "answer": "Rock.",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_36",
    "question": "Vladimir Tsirelson is one of the pioneers in which area of study?",
    "answer": "Quantum Crystallography",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_37",
    "question": "How many seasons did Brian Leetch play in the NHL?",
    "answer": "18 seasons",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_38",
    "question": "In what year did Leandra Leal act in the miniseries A Muralha?",
    "answer": "2000",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_39",
    "question": "What color can the skin of the Santa Catarina tree toad's back be?",
    "answer": "Brown or gray",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_40",
    "question": "What was the reported effect on rental vacancy rates in Vancouver after implementing the empty home tax?",
    "answer": "increased by only 0.1%",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_41",
    "question": "What does the excerpt imply about hope for humankind?",
    "answer": "The writer believes in hope for humankind.",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_42",
    "question": "Which prominent figure led a popular uprising in London during 1196?",
    "answer": "William Fitz Osbern.",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_43",
    "question": "What is the population of Dongguan as of the end of 2012?",
    "answer": "8.29 million",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_44",
    "question": "What is the name of the military base located in Las Vegas, Nevada?",
    "answer": "Nellis Air Force Base",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_45",
    "question": "What was the population of Zapata County in 2020?",
    "answer": "13,889",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_46",
    "question": "What major function is typically associated with the prefrontal cortex?",
    "answer": "Executive function",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_47",
    "question": "What is the full name of Raymond Séguy?",
    "answer": "Raymond Gaston Joseph Séguy",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_48",
    "question": "In which region did Arthur Moulin serve as a member of the National Assembly?",
    "answer": "Nord",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_49",
    "question": "What area does the SL4 connect with its stops?",
    "answer": "Dudley Station and South Station",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_50",
    "question": "Which municipality is the most populous in Winn Parish?",
    "answer": "Winnfield",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_51",
    "question": "What is the name of the mobile role-playing game featuring Disney and Pixar characters?",
    "answer": "Disney Mirrorverse",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_52",
    "question": "What was Robert Storey's role in the Provisional Irish Republican Army?",
    "answer": "Member",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_53",
    "question": "Which group primarily owns the outstations on the eastern side of the border?",
    "answer": "Pitjantjatjara families",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_54",
    "question": "In which film did Norman Lloyd play a Nazi spy?",
    "answer": "Saboteur",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_55",
    "question": "What did Ladislaus Löb specialize in?",
    "answer": "German",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_56",
    "question": "What was Gérard Houllier's role at OL Reign at the time of his death?",
    "answer": "Technical director",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_57",
    "question": "Is documenta a recurring event?",
    "answer": "Yes, it occurs every five years.",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_58",
    "question": "How much can a bull African bush elephant weigh?",
    "answer": "13000 pounds",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_59",
    "question": "Who is the Crown Prince of Saudi Arabia?",
    "answer": "Mohammad bin Salman Al Saud",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_60",
    "question": "What was R. Toros's age at the time of his death?",
    "answer": "85 years",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_61",
    "question": "Where was Ray Perkins born?",
    "answer": "Petal, Mississippi",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_62",
    "question": "Which degree did Hind obtain from University College London?",
    "answer": "Master’s degree in Human Rights",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_63",
    "question": "How old was Tony Conrad at the time of his death?",
    "answer": "76",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_64",
    "question": "Which famous television series did Mae Jemison appear in?",
    "answer": "Star Trek: The Next Generation.",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_65",
    "question": "What significant event caused George II's death?",
    "answer": "Heart problems",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_66",
    "question": "In which year did Telefónica acquire 100% of Tuenti?",
    "answer": "2011",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_67",
    "question": "What was a result of the war between Mexico and the United States between 1846 and 1848?",
    "answer": "Mexico lost its large northern areas",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_68",
    "question": "Who succeeded Masazō Nonaka as the oldest living man?",
    "answer": "Chitetsu Watanabe",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_69",
    "question": "What notable cause is Danny Glover associated with?",
    "answer": "Activism",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_70",
    "question": "What is a polysomnogram?",
    "answer": "A test commonly ordered for some sleep disorders.",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_71",
    "question": "What are examples of 'words' in the self-synchronizing code?",
    "answer": "The sequences of two letters '00' and '11'.",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_72",
    "question": "What country is Pedro Martínez from?",
    "answer": "Dominican Republic",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_73",
    "question": "What year was Earl E. Devaney born?",
    "answer": "1947",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_74",
    "question": "What does Don John convince Claudio of?",
    "answer": "That Hero is cheating on him",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_75",
    "question": "In which year did Miki Ando win the Japanese National Championship for the second time?",
    "answer": "2011",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_76",
    "question": "What was the primary goal of the Israeli pilots during the aerial assault?",
    "answer": "To know the location of each Egyptian jet",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_77",
    "question": "What Grammy Award did J. Cole win?",
    "answer": "Best Rap Song",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_78",
    "question": "What does the name Dinocephalosaurus mean?",
    "answer": "terrible headed lizard",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_79",
    "question": "What was the primary genre of Holly Dunn's music?",
    "answer": "Country music",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_80",
    "question": "In what year did Theresa May begin her career at the Bank of England?",
    "answer": "1977",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_81",
    "question": "What is required for prosecuting a Councillor for crimes related to official capacity?",
    "answer": "The assent of the Federal Assembly.",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_82",
    "question": "Norte de Santander borders which country?",
    "answer": "Venezuela",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_83",
    "question": "Courtney Thorne-Smith is an actress from which country?",
    "answer": "United States",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_84",
    "question": "What is the fictional address of Archie and Edith's house?",
    "answer": "704 Hauser",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_85",
    "question": "What was the capital of all three duchies of Saxe-Eisenach?",
    "answer": "Eisenach",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_86",
    "question": "What feature distinguishes the pig-nosed turtle's flippers?",
    "answer": "Broad paddle-like flippers with two claws",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_87",
    "question": "Which band is Berkeley known as the native city of?",
    "answer": "Green Day.",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_88",
    "question": "What style of text is used in the Doge meme?",
    "answer": "Broken English",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_89",
    "question": "What was Osman Cavcı's first movie role?",
    "answer": "Hababam Sınıfı Güle Güle",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_90",
    "question": "Which of these aircraft was not listed as a user of the Alfa Romeo 135?",
    "answer": "Boeing B-17",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_91",
    "question": "What role does Zoe Kazan primarily hold in the entertainment industry?",
    "answer": "Actress",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_92",
    "question": "When did the Heritage Lottery Fund start accepting applications?",
    "answer": "1994",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_93",
    "question": "Which of the following states is located to the east of the pecan's native range?",
    "answer": "North Carolina",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_94",
    "question": "Who is the most famous user of a blue box?",
    "answer": "John Draper",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_95",
    "question": "In what year was the Constitution of the Empire of Japan enacted?",
    "answer": "1889-1890",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_96",
    "question": "What type of soil is found around Ayiroor?",
    "answer": "Very fertile",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_97",
    "question": "What is Spartanburg's rank by population size in South Carolina?",
    "answer": "12th-largest city by population",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_98",
    "question": "What is the debate surrounding the Gutians focused on?",
    "answer": "Their linguistic roots",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_99",
    "question": "Who is known for being a former U.S. Secretary of State?",
    "answer": "Henry Kissinger",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_100",
    "question": "In what century was lawn tennis invented?",
    "answer": "mid 19th-century",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_101",
    "question": "What type of game is Rhythm Tengoku?",
    "answer": "It is a music mini-game collection.",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_102",
    "question": "What is said to have caused the destruction of the Hanging Gardens?",
    "answer": "An earthquake",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_103",
    "question": "Which beach is the most popular on the island?",
    "answer": "Myrtos",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_104",
    "question": "What was the birth year of Philip of Hesse-Darmstadt?",
    "answer": "1671",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_105",
    "question": "What genre is the movie Jaal classified as?",
    "answer": "Musical and romantic",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_106",
    "question": "What financial trouble did Dharma Arthur face after losing her job?",
    "answer": "Struggling to keep her house out of foreclosure",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_107",
    "question": "When did Christiaan Petit pass away?",
    "answer": "26 December 1984",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_108",
    "question": "Which groups are included in the Somali diaspora?",
    "answer": "Ethnic Somalis",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_109",
    "question": "What are the most common gases in the interstellar medium?",
    "answer": "Hydrogen and helium",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_110",
    "question": "In what year did Goya return to Spain after living in France?",
    "answer": "1826",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_111",
    "question": "What kind of deletion can lead to data loss?",
    "answer": "Accidental deletion.",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_112",
    "question": "What event was occurring during the time of her death?",
    "answer": "COVID-19 pandemic",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_113",
    "question": "When was the Herald Sun first published?",
    "answer": "8 October 1990.",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_114",
    "question": "What was the location style of Tel Aviv that included Aliya Market?",
    "answer": "The White City",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_115",
    "question": "What is one of the components of the Yuva Puraskar?",
    "answer": "A cash prize of Rs. 50,000",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_116",
    "question": "What type of firearms most commonly use belts?",
    "answer": "Machine guns.",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_117",
    "question": "What is one of Alfonso Sastre's best-known plays?",
    "answer": "Death Squad",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_118",
    "question": "What is the primary administrative division of St. Gallen in Switzerland?",
    "answer": "Canton",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_119",
    "question": "What is Mary Jane Veloso's claimed status regarding her charges?",
    "answer": "Innocent",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_120",
    "question": "What year did Jonathan Shurberg die?",
    "answer": "2017",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_121",
    "question": "In what year did Asaph Hall discover the two moons of Mars?",
    "answer": "1877",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_122",
    "question": "Which region does the Bay of Bengal border?",
    "answer": "Bangladesh",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_123",
    "question": "What year was Harry Caray born?",
    "answer": "1914",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_124",
    "question": "In what year was Rochester Cathedral originally founded?",
    "answer": "604 AD",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_125",
    "question": "Who considers Saint Peter a saint?",
    "answer": "Roman Catholic Church",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_126",
    "question": "What is the length of the Susquehanna River?",
    "answer": "At long, it is the longest river on the East Coast.",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_127",
    "question": "How many initial cases of COVID-19 were confirmed in Burundi on 31 March?",
    "answer": "Two cases",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_128",
    "question": "What significant achievement did Oribe Peralta accomplish at the 2012 Olympic football tournament?",
    "answer": "Scored two goals in the final match",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_129",
    "question": "Which piece of dance music is François-Joseph Gossec famous for?",
    "answer": "Tambourin",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_130",
    "question": "How many municipalities are there in Völkermarkt District?",
    "answer": "13",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_131",
    "question": "What was the cause of Emmett W. Chappelle's death?",
    "answer": "Kidney failure",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_132",
    "question": "How many doubles finals has Mary Joe Fernández participated in on the WTA Tour?",
    "answer": "43",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_133",
    "question": "What distinction did Seven Kings High School receive from Ofsted in 2007?",
    "answer": "Grade 1 or an 'outstanding'",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_134",
    "question": "What position did 'Yellow Flicker Beat' reach in Canada?",
    "answer": "Number 21",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_135",
    "question": "In which year did Emmett Hulcy Tidd retire from the Navy?",
    "answer": "1976",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_136",
    "question": "How old was Dave Adolph when he died?",
    "answer": "79",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_137",
    "question": "Which of the following is an application of buoyancy?",
    "answer": "Balloons and blimps using lighter-than-air gases.",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_138",
    "question": "When was Allan Savory born?",
    "answer": "15 September 1935",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_139",
    "question": "What action did the editor of Aqlame take regarding Mohamed's article?",
    "answer": "The article was taken down.",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_140",
    "question": "What is the name of the album released by Saving Abel in 2014?",
    "answer": "Blood Stained Revolution",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_141",
    "question": "What was the name of Aristotle Onassis's luxury yacht?",
    "answer": "Christina",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_142",
    "question": "How many significant battles are mentioned that were fought by the Army of the Cumberland?",
    "answer": "Three",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_143",
    "question": "What year did Taeyeon join SM the Ballad?",
    "answer": "2014",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_144",
    "question": "How many years was McNair's contract that he signed after the Super Bowl season?",
    "answer": "Six years",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_145",
    "question": "What is an affix?",
    "answer": "A piece added to a word that signals or changes its role in a sentence.",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_146",
    "question": "What relationship did Pallas have with Crius?",
    "answer": "Son",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_147",
    "question": "What is the required reaction time for an airbag system?",
    "answer": "Around 1 millisecond.",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_148",
    "question": "Who returned the Pearl Sword to the Lord Mayor of London during their visit in 1641?",
    "answer": "Charles I",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_149",
    "question": "When did Hyun Soong-jong celebrate his last birthday?",
    "answer": "February 26, 2020",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_150",
    "question": "Where was Michael Glawogger born?",
    "answer": "Graz",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_151",
    "question": "How many species are there in the genus Eleutherodactylus?",
    "answer": "185",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_152",
    "question": "What primary purpose does a hydrogen economy serve?",
    "answer": "To replace the use of petroleum",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_153",
    "question": "When was Kadir Mısıroğlu born?",
    "answer": "24 January 1933",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_154",
    "question": "How old was Paul Matters when he died?",
    "answer": "68 years old",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_155",
    "question": "Which army did Monroe Hayward serve in during the Civil War?",
    "answer": "Union Army",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_156",
    "question": "In what city is Hunan Broadcasting System Radio and Television Center located?",
    "answer": "Changsha",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_157",
    "question": "In which region of Maryland is Hagerstown located?",
    "answer": "Western Maryland",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_158",
    "question": "In what year did June Jackson begin her tenure at the Manukau Urban Māori Authority?",
    "answer": "1986",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_159",
    "question": "What major resource is primarily derived from Kimmeridge clay?",
    "answer": "Oil fields in the North Sea",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_160",
    "question": "Which Farmington is listed on the National Register of Historic Places in King and Queen County?",
    "answer": "Farmington (St. Stephens Church, Virginia)",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_161",
    "question": "What types of bodies of water can house a marina?",
    "answer": "Canals and rivers",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_162",
    "question": "How old was Tom Veitch at the time of his death?",
    "answer": "80 years old",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_163",
    "question": "Which country does Raphael Bouju represent?",
    "answer": "Netherlands",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_164",
    "question": "What does religious conservatism apply to politics?",
    "answer": "A specific religion.",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_165",
    "question": "When was the Siilinjärvi carbonatite complex discovered?",
    "answer": "In 1950.",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_166",
    "question": "What is another term for a television movie?",
    "answer": "television film",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_167",
    "question": "What does the name 'Oceanus' mean in Latin?",
    "answer": "ocean",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_168",
    "question": "What has the Vale of Glamorgan Railway recently done due to the breakdown of talks with Cambrian Transport?",
    "answer": "Sold assets",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_169",
    "question": "Who was an Australian poet and critic born in Nabiac?",
    "answer": "Leslie Allan Murray",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_170",
    "question": "How many species of dermestids are estimated to exist?",
    "answer": "500 to 700 species",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_171",
    "question": "What does chemical composition refer to?",
    "answer": "The arrangement, type, and ratio of atoms in molecules of chemical substances.",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_172",
    "question": "What must an orchestra do if they are playing with a piano soloist?",
    "answer": "Tune to the A of the piano",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_173",
    "question": "Which American writer born in January 1921 is known for the novel 'Strangers on a Train'?",
    "answer": "Patricia Highsmith",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_174",
    "question": "Who was the eldest son of Japanese Emperor Richū?",
    "answer": "Ichinobe-no Oshiwa",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_175",
    "question": "Which character did George Gebhardt portray?",
    "answer": "Confederate Soldier",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_176",
    "question": "Where was Margaret imprisoned after the Battle of Tewkesbury?",
    "answer": "Tower of London",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_177",
    "question": "What was the cause of Anne Donovan's death?",
    "answer": "Heart failure",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_178",
    "question": "What is the title of Phil Collins' eighth and final studio album?",
    "answer": "Going Back",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_179",
    "question": "What method did Nadya Suleman use to conceive the octuplets?",
    "answer": "In vitro fertilization",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_180",
    "question": "Who currently leads the Advanced Light Source?",
    "answer": "Roger Falcone",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_181",
    "question": "In Betts v. Brady, who ruled that Betts would not receive a free lawyer?",
    "answer": "The judge presiding over the case.",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_182",
    "question": "Which flower is associated with January?",
    "answer": "Carnation",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_183",
    "question": "What component do phospholipids contain that is significant?",
    "answer": "Phosphorus",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_184",
    "question": "What was the nickname of Max Gros-Louis?",
    "answer": "Oné Onti",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_185",
    "question": "In which year was J. Michael Straczynski born?",
    "answer": "1954",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_186",
    "question": "Which artistic style is Fallen London compared to?",
    "answer": "Romanticism",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_187",
    "question": "What serious injury did Poste suffer in a car accident?",
    "answer": "Severe skull and brain injuries",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_188",
    "question": "What region is formed with Bangladesh and West Bengal?",
    "answer": "Bengal",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_189",
    "question": "What is the modern French name for the passenger pigeon?",
    "answer": "Pigeon migrateur.",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_190",
    "question": "What is a programming feature that JLTV offers?",
    "answer": "On-demand programming",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_191",
    "question": "What web series features Jason Griffith as the character Cal?",
    "answer": "Casters",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_192",
    "question": "Which structure marks the transition between hotel and residential use on Beetham Tower?",
    "answer": "A four-metre cantilever.",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_193",
    "question": "What is the full name of the character known as Rocky?",
    "answer": "Rocket 'Rocky' J. Squirrel",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_194",
    "question": "What Dover is located in Pennsylvania?",
    "answer": "Dover, Pennsylvania",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_195",
    "question": "What year was Striking Distance released?",
    "answer": "1993",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_196",
    "question": "In what way can compiled code be stored for later processing?",
    "answer": "Each compilation step’s product can be stored incrementally.",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_197",
    "question": "In what year did Dvořák die?",
    "answer": "1904",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_198",
    "question": "What position did Horst Seehofer hold from 1992 to 1998?",
    "answer": "Federal Minister for Health and Social Security",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_199",
    "question": "What condition was Semmelweis suspected to have later in life?",
    "answer": "Alzheimer’s disease",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_200",
    "question": "What is the relationship between Mandodari Parab and Abhijeet?",
    "answer": "Mandodari Parab is the restaurant manager of Abhijeet.",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_201",
    "question": "According to the excerpt, emotions are associated with which of the following?",
    "answer": "Feeling, mood, temperament, personality, disposition, and motivation.",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_202",
    "question": "How long did Siddhi Savetsila serve as Deputy Prime Minister?",
    "answer": "8 months",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_203",
    "question": "What alcohol can be sometimes made from molasses besides rum?",
    "answer": "Vodka",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_204",
    "question": "Which country is Lee Tamahori from?",
    "answer": "New Zealand",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_205",
    "question": "What was the name of the electorate Jacinda Ardern represented from 2017 to 2023?",
    "answer": "Mount Albert",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_206",
    "question": "Which team did Jordan Schroeder begin his professional career with?",
    "answer": "Vancouver Canucks",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_207",
    "question": "Which office suite can optionally be added to Damn Small Linux?",
    "answer": "OpenOffice.org",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_208",
    "question": "What type of shrines ranked below 'District shrines'?",
    "answer": "Village shrines",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_209",
    "question": "On which river does Mingora lie?",
    "answer": "River Swat",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_210",
    "question": "What does 'Kokkai-gijidōmae' translate to in English?",
    "answer": "In front of National Diet Building.",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_211",
    "question": "What was one of John Kenneth Galbraith's roles in the government?",
    "answer": "Public official",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_212",
    "question": "How many Academy Awards did Dalton Trumbo win while blacklisted?",
    "answer": "Two",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_213",
    "question": "What is the title of the book that earned Virginia Hamilton the U.S. National Book Award?",
    "answer": "M. C. Higgins, the Great",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_214",
    "question": "During which centuries did the Vikings travel to Europe?",
    "answer": "From the 8th to the 11th centuries",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_215",
    "question": "What type of musical piece is Finlandia classified as?",
    "answer": "Symphonic poem",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_216",
    "question": "What is one of the historical martial arts mentioned in the text?",
    "answer": "Pankration.",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_217",
    "question": "Who volunteered to spy during the American Revolutionary War in 1776?",
    "answer": "Nathan Hale",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_218",
    "question": "What was the currency of Czechoslovakia?",
    "answer": "Czechoslovak koruna",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_219",
    "question": "Where do Ranoidea chloris lay their eggs?",
    "answer": "In bodies of water",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_220",
    "question": "What significant cosmic events is the DARE mission aimed to observe?",
    "answer": "Formation of the first stars and reionization of the universe",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_221",
    "question": "What is the full name of the Canadian politician known as Kennedy Stewart?",
    "answer": "Edward Charles Kennedy Stewart",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_222",
    "question": "Which national cricket team did Fletcher coach from 1999 to 2007?",
    "answer": "England cricket team",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_223",
    "question": "What happens when an electron makes a quantum jump?",
    "answer": "It disappears from one orbit and appears in another.",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_224",
    "question": "In which city does Gretchen Whitmer currently reside?",
    "answer": "East Lansing",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_225",
    "question": "What is the primary concern that led to relocating Singapore’s airport to Changi?",
    "answer": "Not enough space for growth",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_226",
    "question": "Who is known for mixing Confucianism with Shinto?",
    "answer": "Yamazaki Ansai",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_227",
    "question": "What does 'Yumjao' mean in Meitei language?",
    "answer": "Large house or big house.",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_228",
    "question": "What happens if teams from the same group are drawn for the round of 16, quarter-finals, or semi-finals?",
    "answer": "They can be drawn against each other.",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_229",
    "question": "What is the name of the album that contains 'Labelled with Love'?",
    "answer": "East Side Story",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_230",
    "question": "Mitte was part of which side of Berlin?",
    "answer": "East Berlin",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_231",
    "question": "What was the last church Denton Lotz served as Senior Pastor?",
    "answer": "Tremont Temple Baptist Church",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_232",
    "question": "Before joining Fox News, which network did she team up with?",
    "answer": "CBS News",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_233",
    "question": "When did the pre-season testing start for this season?",
    "answer": "Immediately after the 2011 Abu Dhabi Grand Prix",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_234",
    "question": "Where is West Side Park located?",
    "answer": "West side of Chicago",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_235",
    "question": "What is a common example of an 'as a service' offering?",
    "answer": "Software as a Service (SaaS).",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_236",
    "question": "Which historical phenomenon is the Inclosure Act associated with?",
    "answer": "The agrarian revolution",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_237",
    "question": "How many years did Brandon Jones play in the NFL?",
    "answer": "5 years",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_238",
    "question": "Which character is the president of Caduceus USA?",
    "answer": "Robert Hoffman",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_239",
    "question": "How many children does Prince Joachim have?",
    "answer": "Four",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_240",
    "question": "In which year did Simone Inzaghi play for Atalanta?",
    "answer": "2007/08",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_241",
    "question": "What year was the song first released?",
    "answer": "1974",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_242",
    "question": "Which difficulty level in Quake can only be accessed in a secret area?",
    "answer": "Nightmare",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_243",
    "question": "How long did the Kiyomihara Palace serve as the capital?",
    "answer": "672–694",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_244",
    "question": "At which event was the Tamil translation of the station name acknowledged as incorrect?",
    "answer": "Downtown MRT Line Stage 2 open house",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_245",
    "question": "The Battle of Mutina is categorized as what type of victory for Antony?",
    "answer": "Strategic victory",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_246",
    "question": "Which area does the Ozarks extend westward into?",
    "answer": "Northeast Oklahoma",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_247",
    "question": "Which region is NOT mentioned as a habitat for Andriasa contraria?",
    "answer": "Deserts",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_248",
    "question": "What is the capital of the arrondissement of Cahors?",
    "answer": "Cahors",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_249",
    "question": "What role do events play in communities?",
    "answer": "They bring people together for shared experiences.",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_250",
    "question": "Which branch is represented by the Rabbit in the Chinese zodiac?",
    "answer": "卯",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_251",
    "question": "What actions did Trump and his allies take following the election?",
    "answer": "They filed many unsuccessful lawsuits to change the results.",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_252",
    "question": "Which positions did Matchick primarily play?",
    "answer": "Infielder",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_253",
    "question": "What rating did the movie receive from Metacritic?",
    "answer": "48 out of 100",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_254",
    "question": "What nickname is commonly used for Singapore due to its greenery?",
    "answer": "Garden City",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_255",
    "question": "How many Tony Awards has Audra McDonald won?",
    "answer": "Six",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_256",
    "question": "Who makes a special guest appearance as Vice President Hal Gardner?",
    "answer": "Ray Wise",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_257",
    "question": "What are the professions of Maejor?",
    "answer": "Record producer, rapper, singer, songwriter",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_258",
    "question": "What was a significant industry in Cymmer?",
    "answer": "Coal mining",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_259",
    "question": "Who appoints the District Secretaries in Sri Lanka?",
    "answer": "the central government",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_260",
    "question": "Which bone is the upper arm bone that connects at the elbow?",
    "answer": "Humerus",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_261",
    "question": "When was Brad Delson born?",
    "answer": "December 1, 1977",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_262",
    "question": "What was the DRP's stance towards Adolf Hitler?",
    "answer": "It did not want to be associated with him.",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_263",
    "question": "What role did Sonny Landham play in the movie Predator?",
    "answer": "Billy Sole",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_264",
    "question": "During which years did Jerry Sheindlin serve on The People's Court?",
    "answer": "1999 to 2000",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_265",
    "question": "What type of area is Telford classified as?",
    "answer": "Census-designated place and unincorporated community",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_266",
    "question": "In what year did Lavori Publici FC officially start participating in the Somalia first league championship?",
    "answer": "1952",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_267",
    "question": "How far is Central Mount Stuart from the Stuart Highway?",
    "answer": "About 6 km.",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_268",
    "question": "In which year was the official name of Windows Server 2008 announced?",
    "answer": "2007",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_269",
    "question": "What was the fate of the Chulkhurst twins?",
    "answer": "They died in 1134",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_270",
    "question": "Who was Hooke's notable rival in the scientific community?",
    "answer": "Isaac Newton",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_271",
    "question": "What efforts were made to protect cultural heritage during the flooding?",
    "answer": "Prevent damage to archaeological sites",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_272",
    "question": "What is the title of the event held in 2020?",
    "answer": "Games of the III Olympiad",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_273",
    "question": "Which category is NOT mentioned as a type of artwork eligible for the competition?",
    "answer": "Performance art",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_274",
    "question": "What is the total area covered by Dadra and Nagar Haveli and Daman and Diu?",
    "answer": "603 sq km",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_275",
    "question": "What is Eddystone categorized as?",
    "answer": "a borough in Delaware County",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_276",
    "question": "What type of beverages are classified as diet sodas?",
    "answer": "Sugar-free carbonated beverages",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_277",
    "question": "What is the capital of Ukraine?",
    "answer": "Kyiv",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_278",
    "question": "When was Balázs Birtalan born?",
    "answer": "October 12, 1969",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_279",
    "question": "Where is Boca Raton located?",
    "answer": "Southern Palm Beach County, Florida",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_280",
    "question": "When was Rafael Ishkhanyan born?",
    "answer": "9 March 1922",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_281",
    "question": "What constitutional article states the requirements for the Presidency?",
    "answer": "Article 72",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_282",
    "question": "In what year was the cover version of 'Mad World' released?",
    "answer": "2001",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_283",
    "question": "What is the brightest star in the constellation of Cygnus?",
    "answer": "Deneb",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_284",
    "question": "What happened to Judah Maccabee in the end?",
    "answer": "He died in combat",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_285",
    "question": "What significant impact did Cuvier have on the concept of organic forms?",
    "answer": "He believed there was no evidence for their evolution.",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_286",
    "question": "What position did Rick Rypien play in ice hockey?",
    "answer": "Centre",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_287",
    "question": "Which organization did Elizabeth Mrema work for before joining UNEP?",
    "answer": "Tanzania's Ministry of Foreign Affairs and International Cooperation",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_288",
    "question": "How is a somersault executed in mid-air?",
    "answer": "By moving the feet over the head.",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_289",
    "question": "Who was the first to observe red blood cells under a microscope?",
    "answer": "Jan Swammerdam",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_290",
    "question": "Which concentration camp did Erich Wasicky work at?",
    "answer": "Mauthausen",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_291",
    "question": "Which stadium is located in Oslo?",
    "answer": "Ullevål Stadion",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_292",
    "question": "What is the nature of the relationships depicted in this genre?",
    "answer": "Often exploitative and non-consensual.",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_293",
    "question": "What is the main objective in the first part of the game?",
    "answer": "To get the most words after four rounds",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_294",
    "question": "What major social event began in the United States around 1946?",
    "answer": "Baby boom",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_295",
    "question": "Which team did the Warriors lose to in the 2016 NBA Finals?",
    "answer": "Cleveland Cavaliers",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_296",
    "question": "In the reaction catalyzed by hexokinase, which molecule acts as the phosphate donor?",
    "answer": "ATP",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_297",
    "question": "What was the name of the defending champions in the competition?",
    "answer": "FC Wacker Innsbruck",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_298",
    "question": "Where is Grand Forks International Airport located?",
    "answer": "Grand Forks, North Dakota",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_299",
    "question": "What is the average altitude in Nontron?",
    "answer": "an unspecified average altitude",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_300",
    "question": "Which species is mentioned as having returned due to improved water quality?",
    "answer": "Brown trout.",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_301",
    "question": "What is Harry's attitude towards Pakhi?",
    "answer": "He starts to like her",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_302",
    "question": "Which state did Chaturvedi govern from 2002 to 2007?",
    "answer": "Karnataka",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_303",
    "question": "Which election did Gore win despite the outcome of the electoral college?",
    "answer": "The national popular vote",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_304",
    "question": "What type of ion does thallium(I) fluoride contain?",
    "answer": "fluoride ions",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_305",
    "question": "Which of the following languages have Annalena McAfee's children's books been translated into?",
    "answer": "French, German, and Dutch",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_306",
    "question": "Is an autoregressive model used in statistics?",
    "answer": "Yes",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_307",
    "question": "Which fields do toxicologists rely on in their work?",
    "answer": "Biology, chemistry, pharmacology, and medicine.",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_308",
    "question": "How many non-voting delegates were elected alongside the House members?",
    "answer": "Six non-voting delegates",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_309",
    "question": "What is the main activity at oil refineries involving fractional distillation?",
    "answer": "Separating crude oil into various components",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_310",
    "question": "Which political party did Marion Barry belong to?",
    "answer": "Democratic Party",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_311",
    "question": "Which area is known as part of the Anglican Diocese of Durham?",
    "answer": "Sunderland",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_312",
    "question": "County Tipperary is named after which town?",
    "answer": "Tipperary",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_313",
    "question": "What was the primary action taken by Bhagat Singh and his partner during the assembly incident?",
    "answer": "Bombed the Central Legislative Assembly",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_314",
    "question": "Which Major League Baseball team did Oscar Gamble play for on two separate occasions?",
    "answer": "New York Yankees",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_315",
    "question": "What year did the band Mud form?",
    "answer": "1966",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_316",
    "question": "What was the outcome of the High Court of Australia regarding Oceania House?",
    "answer": "The government could not buy it.",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_317",
    "question": "What is the title of Brahmagupta's work translated as 'correctly established doctrine of Brahma'?",
    "answer": "Brāhmasphuṭasiddhānta",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_318",
    "question": "What genre of television is Jerzy Gruza's work associated with?",
    "answer": "Comedy and drama",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_319",
    "question": "What medical condition did Gary Coleman suffer from?",
    "answer": "Nephritis",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_320",
    "question": "Who founded Omega SA?",
    "answer": "Louis Brandt",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_321",
    "question": "Which station is no longer operational in the given excerpt?",
    "answer": "Croft railway station at Croft",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_322",
    "question": "Who built the notable structure White Nancy?",
    "answer": "The Gaskell family",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_323",
    "question": "Which languages are predominantly spoken in Java?",
    "answer": "Javanese language and other languages",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_324",
    "question": "How old was Richard Schifter when he died?",
    "answer": "97",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_325",
    "question": "For how many years did Neil Lennon represent Northern Ireland?",
    "answer": "Nine years",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_326",
    "question": "During which conflict did the members of the Grand Army of the Republic serve?",
    "answer": "American Civil War",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_327",
    "question": "What is the nickname of Kazuo Matsui?",
    "answer": "Kaz",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_328",
    "question": "What year did Brenden Aaronson make his debut for Red Bull Salzburg?",
    "answer": "2021",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_329",
    "question": "Which book is considered Alcott's most famous work?",
    "answer": "Little Women",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_330",
    "question": "In which decade was Norman Bates introduced as a fictional character?",
    "answer": "1950s",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_331",
    "question": "What are the main components of a Choco Pie?",
    "answer": "Two layers of cake with marshmallow filling and chocolate coating",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_332",
    "question": "What was Nelle Wilson Reagan's ancestry?",
    "answer": "Scots-English",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_333",
    "question": "What does the language Mida'a represent in the classifications?",
    "answer": "< B.1",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_334",
    "question": "What kind of consultation did the crew for Ratatouille seek?",
    "answer": "Advice from chefs",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_335",
    "question": "What is a dominant characteristic of Modern Orthodoxy in Israel?",
    "answer": "It is dominated by Religious Zionism.",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_336",
    "question": "Which of the following best describes the behavior of consumers of Veblen goods?",
    "answer": "They consume more as the good's price rises.",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_337",
    "question": "What instrument did Hamdi Benani play?",
    "answer": "Violin",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_338",
    "question": "Who plays the character Carol in Foreign Correspondent?",
    "answer": "Laraine Day",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_339",
    "question": "Which highway does Highway 20 intersect with?",
    "answer": "Highway 4",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_340",
    "question": "Which artist created the statue of David for Florence Cathedral?",
    "answer": "Michelangelo",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_341",
    "question": "When was Pretty. Odd. released?",
    "answer": "March 25, 2008",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_342",
    "question": "What classification is explicitly excluded from the Reptiliomorpha clade?",
    "answer": "Synapsids",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_343",
    "question": "What influenced Aram Khachaturian's music?",
    "answer": "Folk music of Armenia",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_344",
    "question": "What war did Henry III face during his reign starting in 1264?",
    "answer": "the Second Barons' War",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_345",
    "question": "Which historical figure is associated with the name 'Vizhupparaiyar'?",
    "answer": "Aadhinathan Vizhupparaiyan is associated with the name 'Vizhupparaiyar'.",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_346",
    "question": "In which city is the Operation Boatswain Memorial located?",
    "answer": "Jerusalem",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_347",
    "question": "In what year did Kobe Bryant retire from professional basketball?",
    "answer": "2016",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_348",
    "question": "What was the name of the newspaper Bhagat Singh published in Delhi?",
    "answer": "Daily Veer Arjun",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_349",
    "question": "What do most pagans focus on in their beliefs?",
    "answer": "Spirituality and nature",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_350",
    "question": "In which city did Marian Duś pass away?",
    "answer": "Warsaw",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_351",
    "question": "Which single helped Teairra Marí redeem her career?",
    "answer": "Hunt 4 U",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_352",
    "question": "What was the B-side track for the 1985 7\" single release?",
    "answer": "Angels Don't Fall in Love",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_353",
    "question": "What country is Santa Fe de Antioquia located in?",
    "answer": "Colombia",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_354",
    "question": "Which illness did Giuseppe Virgili die from?",
    "answer": "An illness",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_355",
    "question": "What was Tammany Hall originally called?",
    "answer": "The Society of St. Tammany.",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_356",
    "question": "Which type of fossil comparison was used in recent studies of Kronosaurus?",
    "answer": "Comparison to other pliosaurs",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_357",
    "question": "What was the date of birth of József Halzl?",
    "answer": "19 December 1933",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_358",
    "question": "Which team did Stewart Downing join after leaving Middlesbrough?",
    "answer": "Aston Villa",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_359",
    "question": "What was Harry Perkowski's birth date?",
    "answer": "September 6, 1922",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_360",
    "question": "What does the term 'on loan' refer to in the context of exhibitions?",
    "answer": "Objects specifically borrowed from other museums.",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_361",
    "question": "Which of the following is a song listed along with 'Louie Louie'?",
    "answer": "Motörhead songs",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_362",
    "question": "Who directed the movie Miranda?",
    "answer": "Ken Annakin",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_363",
    "question": "What is another area Saint Martin de Porres is the patron saint of?",
    "answer": "Race relations",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_364",
    "question": "What was the total number of confirmed Covid-19 cases in Florida referenced?",
    "answer": "Over 5 million",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_365",
    "question": "What major health issue did Larry Fine experience during the production of Kook's Tour?",
    "answer": "Suffered a stroke",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_366",
    "question": "What is the release year of John Wesley Harding's album titled 'Adam's Apple'?",
    "answer": "2004",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_367",
    "question": "How quickly does insulin aspart begin to work?",
    "answer": "In minutes",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_368",
    "question": "What is a semi-trailer primarily attached to?",
    "answer": "A tractor unit",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_369",
    "question": "What is the primary role of a point guard in basketball?",
    "answer": "Facilitating the offense",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_370",
    "question": "When did Christopher Kloeble participate in the Ingeborg Bachmann Competition?",
    "answer": "June 2010",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_371",
    "question": "In what year did Andrew Greeley retire?",
    "answer": "2009",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_372",
    "question": "In what year did the Montreux Casino catch fire during a concert?",
    "answer": "1971",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_373",
    "question": "What type of film is Donald's Dog Laundry?",
    "answer": "Short film",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_374",
    "question": "Which company publishes comic books featuring Venom?",
    "answer": "Marvel Comics",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_375",
    "question": "Which of the following sentences correctly uses a present participle?",
    "answer": "The dog is barking happily.",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_376",
    "question": "In which century was '99 Bottles of Beer' written?",
    "answer": "Mid-1900s",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_377",
    "question": "What was the year of Aleksandr Timoshinin's death?",
    "answer": "2021",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_378",
    "question": "In which Paralympics did Pedro Enrique Delgado Martin race in 2000?",
    "answer": "2000 Summer Paralympics",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_379",
    "question": "What was John Polkinghorne's profession at the University of Cambridge?",
    "answer": "Professor of Mathematical Physics",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_380",
    "question": "Which song by Supertramp suggests optimism?",
    "answer": "Give a Little Bit",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_381",
    "question": "How did ear trumpets help people with hearing loss?",
    "answer": "By making sound energy stronger when it hits the ear drum",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_382",
    "question": "What title is held by Altkirch in the Haut-Rhin department?",
    "answer": "Subprefecture",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_383",
    "question": "Which film was co-written by Edgar Wright?",
    "answer": "Ant-Man",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_384",
    "question": "Which actor is featured in A Star Is Born?",
    "answer": "Fredric March",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_385",
    "question": "How many members initially formed Neutral Milk Hotel?",
    "answer": "1",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_386",
    "question": "Which of the following is an example of an instrumental song?",
    "answer": "\"Theme from A Summer Place\" by Percy Faith.",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_387",
    "question": "How many private individual customers did SEB Pank have as of 2004?",
    "answer": "580,000",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_388",
    "question": "Who composed a poem against the partition of Bengal?",
    "answer": "Rabindranath Tagore",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_389",
    "question": "Which symbol is NOT part of the Hindu–Arabic numeral system?",
    "answer": "11",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_390",
    "question": "Which team did Mo Vaughn play for first?",
    "answer": "Boston Red Sox",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_391",
    "question": "How many Stanley Cups had Chicago Blackhawks won after the 2010 Finals?",
    "answer": "Four Stanley Cups",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_392",
    "question": "In which state was Julie Adams born?",
    "answer": "Iowa",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_393",
    "question": "Which work focuses on the experiences of Palestinian refugees during the Lebanese civil war?",
    "answer": "Al-Manam",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_394",
    "question": "What kind of missile can attack helicopters use?",
    "answer": "Nuclear missiles",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_395",
    "question": "When did Sudhakar Chaturvedi die?",
    "answer": "27 February 2020",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_396",
    "question": "What is the Grand Bazaar considered in terms of market type?",
    "answer": "One of the largest covered markets in the world",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_397",
    "question": "In what year was 'Bully Market' published?",
    "answer": "2022",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_398",
    "question": "Which bird symbolizes liberty in the emblem of Guatemala?",
    "answer": "Resplendent quetzal",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_399",
    "question": "What position did Nancy Hollister hold before becoming governor?",
    "answer": "Lieutenant Governor",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_400",
    "question": "What type of organizations do vanguardists form?",
    "answer": "Organizations that manifest proletarian political power",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_401",
    "question": "Which month has the most precipitation in Temuco?",
    "answer": "June",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_402",
    "question": "What episode features Nicole meeting her husband Richard?",
    "answer": "The Choices",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_403",
    "question": "In what decade was 'I Still Miss Someone' first released?",
    "answer": "1950s",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_404",
    "question": "What type of game is L?",
    "answer": "A text adventure game",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_405",
    "question": "When did the new exits at Queenstown MRT Station officially open?",
    "answer": "August 23, 2015",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_406",
    "question": "What foundation did José Carreras establish?",
    "answer": "José Carreras International Leukaemia Foundation",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_407",
    "question": "Which medal did Gowans receive in 1976?",
    "answer": "Royal Medal",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_408",
    "question": "What event did A Quiet Place premiere at?",
    "answer": "South by Southwest",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_409",
    "question": "In which country did the album reach number 1?",
    "answer": "Scotland",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_410",
    "question": "What tool is used to move a boat through the water?",
    "answer": "Oars",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_411",
    "question": "What type of labor was used in factories during World War II in Nuremberg?",
    "answer": "Slave labor",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_412",
    "question": "Where did Sison go into exile?",
    "answer": "Netherlands",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_413",
    "question": "What color is the liquor of the first flush tea?",
    "answer": "Light yellowish-green",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_414",
    "question": "Where is the Hellenic Parliament located?",
    "answer": "Old Royal Palace in Athens",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_415",
    "question": "In which city did Mildred Dresselhaus pass away?",
    "answer": "Cambridge, Massachusetts",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_416",
    "question": "Which league did Jassen Cullimore last participate in?",
    "answer": "Deutsche Eishockey Liga",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_417",
    "question": "What place did the Pimenov brothers finish at the 1988 Olympics?",
    "answer": "6th place",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_418",
    "question": "Which of the following films was released first in Eddie Redmayne's filmography?",
    "answer": "The Good Shepherd",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_419",
    "question": "What type of photography did Ed Ross focus on in his last six years?",
    "answer": "Wet-plate photography",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_420",
    "question": "What is the maximum punishment for high treason in Canada?",
    "answer": "Life in prison.",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_421",
    "question": "What was the nationality of Nicolas Lane Noxon?",
    "answer": "American",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_422",
    "question": "For which team did Dale Davis play the most games?",
    "answer": "Indiana Pacers",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_423",
    "question": "What task have self-driving buses been programmed to do in public places?",
    "answer": "Travel a given route",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_424",
    "question": "What color does Copper(I) bromide turn when exposed to air?",
    "answer": "green",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_425",
    "question": "What underlying condition did the first deceased patient have?",
    "answer": "Diabetes",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_426",
    "question": "How many months have 30 days, including April?",
    "answer": "Four months",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_427",
    "question": "Which character did Gary Beach portray in The Producers?",
    "answer": "Roger De Bris",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_428",
    "question": "In what year did STV begin broadcasting?",
    "answer": "STV started in 2006.",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_429",
    "question": "In which conflict did women first officially participate in the Naval Academy?",
    "answer": "Class of 1980",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_430",
    "question": "What was Lucjan Avgustini's role in the Roman Catholic Church?",
    "answer": "Bishop of the Roman Catholic Diocese of Sapë",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_431",
    "question": "What percentage of households in the top 5% were headed by someone identifying as White alone?",
    "answer": "87.93%",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_432",
    "question": "What field of physics does Pascal's law belong to?",
    "answer": "Fluid mechanics.",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_433",
    "question": "What health issue led to Jimmy Rave's arm being amputated?",
    "answer": "An infection in his left arm",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_434",
    "question": "In what year did Aron Eisenberg pass away?",
    "answer": "2019",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_435",
    "question": "What is Monmouth known for producing historically?",
    "answer": "Monmouth caps, a type of woollen headgear.",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_436",
    "question": "What is the title of the fourth episode in the 30th season of The Simpsons?",
    "answer": "Treehouse of Horror XXIX",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_437",
    "question": "How can you determine if a system can run a specific operating system?",
    "answer": "By checking the system requirements.",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_438",
    "question": "What movement causes Van der Waals forces?",
    "answer": "Electrons moving to one side of an atom.",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_439",
    "question": "What does the term 'scone' potentially derive from in the Gaelic language?",
    "answer": "A piece of dough that has been cooked",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_440",
    "question": "Who appointed Tina Smith to the U.S. Senate?",
    "answer": "Governor Mark Dayton",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_441",
    "question": "What aspect of existence does the poem emphasize?",
    "answer": "Resilience despite struggles",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_442",
    "question": "Where was David Plouffe born?",
    "answer": "Wilmington, Delaware",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_443",
    "question": "What educational institution did Christina Kirkman graduate from in 2015?",
    "answer": "Emerson College",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_444",
    "question": "What character did Valentina Kurdyukova portray?",
    "answer": "Ksanka Shchus",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_445",
    "question": "What year did the Mullsjö Folk High School move to Mullsjö?",
    "answer": "1950",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_446",
    "question": "What is the method of electing the Chairperson of the African Union?",
    "answer": "Consensus or vote by member states",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_447",
    "question": "Which year did the merger occur?",
    "answer": "2012",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_448",
    "question": "What was the duration of Tudor Gunasekara's parliamentary service?",
    "answer": "1977 until 1983",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_449",
    "question": "How many ODIs did Andrew Symonds play for Australia?",
    "answer": "198",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_450",
    "question": "What unique reproductive behavior do ceratiids exhibit?",
    "answer": "Polyandry, with multiple males attached to one female.",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_451",
    "question": "What is the female equivalent title of a baron?",
    "answer": "Baroness",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_452",
    "question": "Who was Geoffrey II's first wife?",
    "answer": "Agnes of Burgundy",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_453",
    "question": "What was Adolfo Mexiac primarily known for?",
    "answer": "Being a Mexican graphic artist.",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_454",
    "question": "When was David Irvine born?",
    "answer": "10 January 1947",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_455",
    "question": "What did the winning team receive for their charity?",
    "answer": "Money",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_456",
    "question": "Where was Kliment Voroshilov buried?",
    "answer": "Kremlin Wall Necropolis",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_457",
    "question": "What is the infinitive form of the verb meaning 'to run'?",
    "answer": "kuri.",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_458",
    "question": "In the film Phantom of the Paradise, what role did Paul Williams take on?",
    "answer": "He wrote the music and starred in the film.",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_459",
    "question": "What educational plan does Hwa Chong Institution operate under?",
    "answer": "The Special Assistance Plan for bilingualism",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_460",
    "question": "What inspired the creation of 'Mystery Train'?",
    "answer": "Earlier songs",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_461",
    "question": "Who was the husband of Suzanne Mubarak?",
    "answer": "Hosni Mubarak",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_462",
    "question": "What notable medal did Jim Ryun win at the 1968 Summer Olympics?",
    "answer": "Silver medal in the 1500 m",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_463",
    "question": "Which Olympic medal did Ghasem Rezaei win in 2012?",
    "answer": "Gold medal",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_464",
    "question": "What position did Röhm hold in the Nazi Party in January 1931?",
    "answer": "Leader of the Sturmabteilung",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_465",
    "question": "Which company distributed the movie?",
    "answer": "Toho",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_466",
    "question": "How long is Burley Park railway station from Headingley Stadium?",
    "answer": "Ten minutes south",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_467",
    "question": "Who wrote the autobiography titled 'My Life'?",
    "answer": "Bill Clinton",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_468",
    "question": "What reality show is Sue Cleaver currently participating in?",
    "answer": "I'm a Celebrity...Get Me Out of Here!",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_469",
    "question": "What is a form of modern exploitation where children are treated as property?",
    "answer": "Child slavery",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_470",
    "question": "What does the excerpt state is required for land to be a permanent body?",
    "answer": "Consolidation of masses and elevation from the sea.",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_471",
    "question": "Which of the following was protected under the Sex Discrimination Act?",
    "answer": "Discrimination on the grounds of sex",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_472",
    "question": "How many axles did the double-decker bus body have options for?",
    "answer": "2 or 3 axles",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_473",
    "question": "What was Hrkac's achievement with the Indianapolis Ice during the 1992–93 season?",
    "answer": "Named league MVP",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_474",
    "question": "How is Rupnagar best described in relation to Mohali?",
    "answer": "Part of its municipal council area",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_475",
    "question": "Which character is portrayed by Anang Desai?",
    "answer": "Tulsidas Parekh (Bapuji)",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_476",
    "question": "Which of the following shows did Terrence Scammell NOT direct?",
    "answer": "Gotham",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_477",
    "question": "What is the name of the Marathi language series produced by Iris Productions?",
    "answer": "Sang Tu Aahes Ka?",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_478",
    "question": "Which album was released by Sten & Stanley in 1985?",
    "answer": "Musik, dans & party",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_479",
    "question": "In which year did Theresa Klein compete in her last listed championship?",
    "answer": "2009",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_480",
    "question": "Which group of plants is described as the largest solar plant of any kind in the world?",
    "answer": "SEGS group of plants",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_481",
    "question": "What does Cantor's diagonal argument demonstrate about the set T?",
    "answer": "It demonstrates that the set T is uncountable.",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_482",
    "question": "During which years was Sharma a member of the Indian Parliament?",
    "answer": "1991 to 2004, and 2010 to 2016",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_483",
    "question": "What does article 639 of the Islamic Penal Code address?",
    "answer": "Punishments for immorality or prostitution.",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_484",
    "question": "What period is known as the Trente Glorieuses?",
    "answer": "Thirty Glorious Years of economic growth between 1945 and 1974",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_485",
    "question": "In which part of Montana is Lewistown located?",
    "answer": "Central Montana",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_486",
    "question": "What significant event took place on September 21, 480 BC?",
    "answer": "The Persians sack Athens",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_487",
    "question": "How did the name 'hardhead' originate?",
    "answer": "From the challenges faced by taxidermists.",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_488",
    "question": "What happens to teams when they start the Championship round?",
    "answer": "Their points from the Regular season are halved, rounded upwards",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_489",
    "question": "What is the birth year of Anders Jacobsson?",
    "answer": "1963",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_490",
    "question": "Which gang was among the last to operate before bushranging declined?",
    "answer": "Kelly Gang led by Ned Kelly",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_491",
    "question": "What geographical area does Huntington Park occupy?",
    "answer": "Southeastern Los Angeles County",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_492",
    "question": "What profession did Madelyn Lee Payne's parents have?",
    "answer": "Stern Methodist parents",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_493",
    "question": "What position did Elisabetta Casellati hold from 2018 to 2022?",
    "answer": "President of the Italian Senate",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_494",
    "question": "What type of damage did Black Sunday cause?",
    "answer": "Economic and agricultural damage",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_495",
    "question": "Which component is part of the balustrade system?",
    "answer": "Pickets.",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_496",
    "question": "Which of the following actors was married to Angelina Jolie?",
    "answer": "Billy Bob Thornton",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_497",
    "question": "What was the primary language spoken in The Bahamas?",
    "answer": "English",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_498",
    "question": "Who began the scholarly study of climate?",
    "answer": "The Greeks.",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_499",
    "question": "How many stars did Roger Ebert give Jason X?",
    "answer": "0.5 stars out of 4",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  },
  {
    "intent": "wiki_question_500",
    "question": "Which letters are considered diacritics in Esperanto?",
    "answer": "ĉ, ĝ, ĥ, ĵ, ŝ, ŭ",
    "createdAt": "2025-10-29T00:00:00Z"
  }
]